要记住  合约(contract)是一个协定  描述了在我们的数据模型
Remember, that a contract is an agreement between our data model and
和视图之间信息如何被存储
our views describing how information is stored.
它包括常量字符串  这些字符串代表了我们的UI将要显示的所有域
It contains constant strings to represent all the fields that our user
在Sunsline的例子中
interface will display, and in the case of Sunshine,
数据库将被存储在这里
that our database will store.
我们仅仅覆盖所有我们将需要在2SQLI数据库里使用的列
We've just covered all the columns that we'll need to
我们用这个数据库来存储天气和信息
use in our 2SQLI databases that will store weather and information.
现在让我们学习这些列名常量是如何在天气contract里声明的
Now let's learn how these column names constraints are declared in our weather
contract.
让我们快速浏览下我们已经提供给你的WeatherContract类文件
Let's take a quick look at the weather contract class file that we've
given you.
这个contract类包含两个内部类  WeatherEntry和LocationEntry
The contract class has two inner classes, WeatherEntry and LocationEntry.
每个内部类都包含定义表的常量字符串
Each of these inner classes contains constant strings that define tables.
现在  我们的WeatherEntry类只含有列常量
Right now, we only have column constants for WeatherEntry,
这个表含有天气预报信息
the table that contains weather forecast information.
第一个常量是TABLE_NAME  对于WeatherEntry来说
The first constant is the TABLE_NAME which, for the WeatherEntry,
是一个简单的单词 weather
is simply the word "weather".
定义在WeatherEntry类里的常量值
The constant values as defined in the WeatherEntry class match the values
要和存储在Weather表里面的值相匹配
we're storing in the weather table.
举个例子  我们已经获得最低气温
For example, we've got minimum temperature,
在这儿定义的是COLUMN_MIN_TEMP
which is defined here as COLUMN_MIN_TEMP.
气压列定义为COLUMN_PRESSURE
Pressure column is defined as COLUMN_PRESSURE.
但是我们还少了一列  这列用来定义唯一ID
But we're missing a column to define the unique ID.
这是因为这个类是继承接口类BaseColumns的
This is because we're implementing the class, BaseColumns,
这个接口里包括一个叫做_ID的常量字符串(值"_id")
which contains a constant called _ID.
通过添加一个_id列来作为数据表的主键  我们便可以利用多种
By adding an _id column to our table as a primary key, we can utilize various
依赖于 已建"_id"列 的Android辅助类
Android helper classes that rely on the _id column being created.
LOC_KEY列就是我们早些时候讨论过的外键
The LOC_KEY column is the foreign key we talked about earlier,
指向Location表里面的记录
that points to records in the location table.
因为实际上列名实际上是不包含数据类型的
Since the column names don't actually contain data types,
所以  一般在在变量名称中使用注解(annotation)来标识这些类型
it's usual to annotate these types in the variable names, and or
或着通过注释(comment)来让我们的合约更加明确
comments to make our contract more explicit